There are many monsters threatening humans.
有许多怪物 威胁着人类
Many brave adventurers stepped forward bravely.
挺身而出的是 众多勇敢的冒险家
And I,
而我
Alvin, is one of them.
埃尔文就是其中一位
Forming a party with the healer Carla,
与僧侣卡菈组队
let's continue the adventure today.
今天也持续冒险旅程
DON'T HURT ME, MY HEALER
(这个僧侣有够烦)
THE TITLE "AFTER MARIA AND ELLIE, THERE WILL ALSO BE FEMALE GUESTS IN THE NEXT EPISODE."
(此次的标题) (继玛丽亚和艾莉 这集又是女性来宾登场的集数)
"THIS SHOW SOMETIMES HAS A DIFFERENT CHRONOLOGICAL ORDER." Found
(话说回来这个节目有时时间顺序不太一样 基本上跟原作差不多) 水晶球是找到了
"BUT FOR THE EPISODE ABOUT MEDUSA AND DRYAD, IT'S RARE TO HAVE SO MANY GIRLS IN ONE EPISODE." But it's not the sword.
(但关于美杜沙和树妖的集数 难得有这么多女孩子的集数) 但这不是剑
"WE SHOULD BROADCAST IT EARLY AND LET THEM APPEAR FOR A FEW EPISODES. IT MAY INCREASE A LOT" It's a statue of a goddess.
(干脆就早点播出 甚至出现个两三集 或许能增加不少人气) 是女神像
"OF POPULARITY. WE INTENDED TO DO SO. BUT IT'LL COST TOO MUCH BUDGET IF WE MAKE A FEW EPISODES." I think so...
(一开始有这样的打算 但也出现做两三集的话会花太多金费) 我想应该是吧…
"AND THE OVERALL PROCESS MAY BECOME MESSY. SO FORGET IT." My crystal ball is broken.
(且整体流程也可能变得乱七八糟的意见 所以还是算了) 我的水晶球都碎了
"THERE ARE SO MANY PRIVATE STORIES LIKE THIS." Because it hit the head of the statue.
(像这种私底下的小故事多到不胜凡举) 因为击中了女神像的头
"FINALLY, WE STILL MADE A GOOD EPISODE NINE." What should we do?
(最后仍制作出满意的第九话) 怎么办
Will we be cursed?
会不会遭天谴
A cleric can't be afraid of curses.
害怕天谴的人无法担任圣职人员
A cleric wouldn't say something like that.
圣职人员才不会说这种话
Who's that?
什么人
A monster.
魔物
Are you the ones who broke my seal?
帮我解开封印的人是你们吗
A seal?
封印
Thank you.
感谢你们
In this way, I can engulf the humans with fear.
如此一来 我便能让人类陷入恐惧之中
Wicked monster.
可恶的魔物
What's wrong?
干嘛啦
She said that stuff. Let's kill her.
她竟然说那种话 我们灭了她吧
This can indeed maintain world peace.
这样的确能保护世界和平
No. The way she spoke pisses me off.
不 是她的口气让人不爽
-Just personal emotion. -Yes.
-凭个人感官 -对
But I lost my sword.
可是 我的剑不见了耶
Look.
你看
She was sealed in such a small cave.
她被封印在那么小的洞穴里
She must be tiny and weak.
一定又小又弱
Maybe she'll be squashed when we step on her.
搞不好一踩就扁了
Are we really going to do it?
真的要这样吗
If anything happens, I'll cover you with Tetsuzanko.
如果有什么万一 我就用铁山靠罩你
Okay. I'll beat you for world peace.
好 为了世界和平我要打倒你
Come out!
出来吧
We'll smash your mouth.
看我们打烂你的臭嘴
How suicidal you are.
真不要命呢
Over there.
在那
I just woke up. Let me improve my skills with you.
我刚睡醒 就拿你们来练练身手吧
No problem. Come out.
没问题 出来啊
How vigorous.
气势真不错
Do you think you can beat me?
你以为真的能赢得了我吗
Let's fight!
一决胜负吧
What monster is that? She's not tiny at all.
那是什么魔物 一点都不小只
What are you doing?
你干嘛啦
Mr. Alvin, be careful.
埃尔文先生 请小心
She's Medusa.
她是美杜莎
Me... Medusa.
美…美杜莎
She'll turn you into a stone if you look at her eyes.
看了他的眼睛就会变成石头
I know.
我知道
Listen. Never look at her eyes.
听好了 绝对不能看她的眼睛
I got it.
我知道啦
Never. Never do that.
绝对绝对哦 绝对不可以哦
You're so annoying.
你很烦耶
Never look at her.
绝对不能看哦
Peek.
偷看
You looked.
你看了
Oh, n...
糟…
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
Is he a fool?
他该不会是笨蛋吧
I'm responsible for him.
我得为他负责
No, he should be responsible for himself.
不是吧 是他该为自己负责
No, I should have noticed that.
不 我早该注意到
I kept warning him. Instead, he might pretend not to hear me.
我一直叮咛他 他反而可能会假装没听到
What's wrong with your thought patterns?
你们的思考模式到底哪里出问题了
Forget it. Turn the girl into a stone too.
算了 女的也变石头吧
Anyway, Mr. Alvin.
话说回来 埃尔文先生
What kind of ordinary posture is this?
这是什么普通的姿势
No matter how I see you, you look like something on the roadside...
不管怎么看 都像一般路边的…
Who's the stone on the roadside?
谁是路边的石头啊
I didn't say so.
我没这么说啊
-But you were going to. -Yes.
-但你打算说 -对
What an unpleasant answer.
真令人不爽的回答
How could he break the petrification?
为什么能解除石化
Right. Why?
对哦 为什么
You...
你…
Once again.
再一次
I won't make the same mistake twice.
相同的错我不会犯两次
Hey, look at me.
喂 看我这啊
What kind of fool would look at you knowing that you'd turn him into a stone?
明知会变成石头 哪个笨蛋还会看你啊
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
Look at me. Just look at me.
看我啊 快看我啦
Mr. Alvin, you made a girl cry.
埃尔文先生惹女生哭了
Bad man.
大坏蛋
You don't have to cry...
没必要哭…
You fool!
笨蛋
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
It works this time.
这次成功了吧
What's wrong with you?
你搞什么啊
Break the petrification like how you did just now.
像刚才那样解除石化啊
Do it again.
再解除一次嘛
Break the petrification with a "pop" like that just now.
像刚才那样"啪"的一声解除石化
Please.
拜托你嘛
Okay? Okay?
好吗好吗
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
Do you think it's fun?
你是不是觉得很好玩啊
How could you break the petrification?
为什么能解除石化啦
Why? Why doesn't it work for you?
为什么 为什么对你没用
My strength is completely useless.
我的优势 完全派不上用场
Crocodile tears again. I won't be tricked.
又假哭 我不会被骗了
You must be upset when your identity is denied.
当自己的特色被否定时 一定很难过吧
Like Mr. Alvin, there's nothing left when he takes off his armour.
就像埃尔文先生 脱掉盔甲后 就什么都不剩了
There's my body left.
会剩下本体
Miss Medusa, don't get frustrated so easily.
美杜莎小姐 别这么容易感到挫折
You just haven't got your strength back because you were sealed.
你只是因为被封印 尚未拿回自己的力量罢了
Is that so?
是这样吗
That's right.
就是这样
Come on. Keep your head up and chest out.
来 抬头挺胸
You're Medusa, the legendary monster.
你是美杜莎 传说中的怪物
In this situation...
照这个情势…
Yes.
是啊
You're right.
你说的没错
I'll do my best!
我要加油
I knew it!
我就知道
So you can't use petrification without making a "hah" sound.
意思是说你不发出"喝"的声音 就无法使出石化咯
If everything I look at will be petrified, it'll affect my life.
看到的东西都会被石化的话 会影响到我的生活
Affect your life?
影响到你的生活
Like this?
这样吗
Hands like this.
手要这样
She's not defensive at all.
一点戒心都没有
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
What's going on?
这是怎么回事
I sensed the smell of evil. So I come to find out.
我感觉到邪恶的气息 过来一探究竟
You're the tree spirit, Dryad.
你是树木精灵 德律阿得
It's you, Medusa, as I expected.
果然是你 梅杜莎
I'm the guardian of this forest.
我是森林管理人
Oh humans, you liberated Medusa. What a sinful thing.
人类啊 你们竟然解放了梅杜莎 如此罪大恶极之事
Wait. I wasn't the one who broke the seal...
等等 解开封印的不是…
Are you making excuses?
你想找借口吗
Shut up, you culprit.
闭嘴 真凶
I found this near the destroyed statue.
我在被破坏的女神像附近 找到了这个
Is it yours?
是你们的东西吗
My crystal ball.
我的水晶球
Evidence here.
取得证词
You must compensate me. I'm angry.
你要赔我 森七七
Are you an obnoxious guest monster?
你是奥客怪吗
I see. You're the one who broke the seal of the statue.
原来如此 就是你破坏了女神像封印
Do you know what you've done?
你知道你做了什么吗
What have I done again?
我又做了什么吗
A long time ago, Medusa brought infinite fear to many villages.
很久以前 美杜莎给许多村庄 带来了无限的恐惧
But you broke her seal.
而你却解开了她的封印
You were amazing.
你很厉害嘛
I was impulsive when I was young.
年轻时比较冲动啦
It seems you're getting tamer.
看样子你变圆滑了
It seems Medusa's power becomes weaker.
看来美杜莎的力量变弱了
Now is a good chance.
现在正是个好机会
You have to take responsibility for defeating Medusa.
你要负起责任打倒美杜莎
She's talking about you. Don't look at me.
她说的是你 别看我
Before that, let Mr. Alvin go first.
在此之前 先放了埃尔文先生吧
I'm sad looking at it.
我看了都觉得难过
Carla...
卡菈…
It seems you don't want to see your partner being humiliated.
看样子你果然不想看到 同伴受尽屈辱的模样
Then defeat Medusa first.
那就先打倒美杜莎吧
Really. Why don't you get it?
真是的 你怎么就是不懂呢
I mean, I don't want to see a man in his thirties being hung in a bondage play.
我是说不想看到30多岁的男人 被吊起来玩束缚PLAY啦
Don't mention bondage play. It makes me embarrassed.
别说束缚PLAY 我会觉得很丢脸
This should be my duty as a beautiful girl.
这应该是属于美少女我的职责
Then switch with me. It must fit you very well.
那就跟我交换吧 一定很适合你
That's sexual harassment.
性骚扰
Are you kidding me?
开什么玩笑
Look. She's getting mad. Very angry.
你看 人家生气了 超怒的
Bondage play on a middle-aged man
中年男性的束缚PLAY
is so great, okay?
超棒的好吗
Miss Dryad?
德律阿得小姐
But only for handsome men, right?
但只限定帅哥对吧
What are you arguing about?
你们在吵什么
I think ugly men make me more excited instead.
我反而觉得长相丑陋的男性 更让我感到兴奋
How's that?
怎么样
Don't tell us your fetish.
请不要公开自己的性癖
Calm down, both of you.
两位冷静点
Only Medusa is more normal. What a hell.
只有美杜莎比较正常 地狱啊
For me, it's great to flirt with young boys.
对我来说 玩弄幼齿男孩超棒的
Young boy complex, don't join the argument.
正太控不要加入争论
Mr. Alvin doesn't match the criteria. Let him go.
埃尔文先生的条件不符 快放开他
I haven't seen his looks. I can't agree.
没看到他的长相 我无法赞同
I like baby faces, too.
我也喜欢娃娃脸
These women...
这些女人…
Then let's see the answer.
那来对答案吧
Stop! What are you doing?
住手 你们要干嘛啦
Weren't we talking about defeating Medusa?
不是在讨论要不要打倒美杜莎吗
Why did it turn out like this...
为什么变成这样…
Hey, say something.
喂 说话啊
At least tell me how you feel about seeing me.
至少说说看到我长相的感想啊
Boring.
没意思
Not interesting.
缺乏趣味
A face I'd forget in two hours.
可能两小时后就会忘掉
Sorry for not meeting your expectations!
抱歉哦不符各位的期待
Sorry. It was my fault.
对不起 是我不好
I'm sorry for asking you to defeat the vicious Medusa.
竟然要求你们打倒凶恶的美杜莎
No. I'm accountable for this as well.
不 说到底我也有责任
About 1%.
1％左右的责任
If you had told me earlier, I would be able to respond as soon as possible.
早说的话 我也能尽早对应
I didn't expect him to be so weak...
没想到 他会这么弱…
I heard that petrifaction doesn't work for him. I thought you could defeat Medusa.
听说石化对他无效 我还以为你们能打倒美杜莎
It seems that I'm too naive.
看来是我太天真了
My strength hasn't been recovered yet. And I was ready to fight hard.
我的实力尚未恢复 还做好了苦战一番的打算
Let me say a few words.
让我说几句话
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
The loser doesn't have the right to speak, okay?
落败之人没资格发言 懂吗
It's too strict.
太严格了吧
Listen. I'm weak indeed.
听我说 我的确很弱
That's right.
没错没错
But don't look at me like this.
但别看我这样
I do heavy training and sword practice every day.
我每天都有做重训和练习挥剑
And?
还有呢
But I didn't win this time.
可是这次却没能打赢
Why is it?
这是为什么呢
One, two, three.
一二三
Why?
为什么
Shut up.
安静
There's only one reason.
原因只有一个
That's because I don't have a sword now.
那就是因为我现在没有剑
You don't have to be quiet now.
现在不用安静啦
I don't think it's a matter of the sword.
我觉得不是剑的问题耶
And why doesn't he have a sword? Isn't he a warrior?
而且他为什么没有剑 他不是战士吗
Could he be a suspicious person in armour?
难道是装备盔甲的可疑人士
Armour is his funny signature point.
盔甲是他的招牌搞笑哏哦
I heard it, especially what Carla said.
我听到了 尤其是卡菈说的内容
There's one if you need a sword.
如果需要剑的话 这里有哦
Deep in the forest, there's a holy sword inserted on the platform.
这座森林深处 有把圣剑插在座台上
A holy sword?
圣剑
Many adventurers tried to pull out the holy sword.
许多冒险家都想拔出那把圣剑
But no one made it.
但却无人成功
When I know that you broke the seal of Medusa,
当我得知美杜莎的封印 被你们解开
Is it chance or luck?
该说是偶然 还是运气好呢
maybe it's the moment for the holy sword to be pulled out.
或许圣剑出鞘的时机终于到来了
Go ahead. It's inside.
去吧 就在里面
That's...
那就是…
the legendary...
传说中的…
holy sword.
圣剑
It's inserted the wrong way.
插反了吧
Hero, please pull out the sword.
勇者 请拔剑吧
It's so hard.
太难拔了吧
Usually, the handle is placed above.
通常都是剑柄在上方啊
Alvin, do you hear me?
埃尔文 听得到吗
Alvin.
埃尔文
-Do you hear my voice? -What's that sound?
-听得到我的声音吗 -什么声音
Could it be...
难道是…
I'm the holy sword.
我是圣剑
Are you really the holy sword?
真的是圣剑吗
Alvin, the hero.
勇者埃尔文
I've been waiting for you.
我一直在等你
I'm the hero. Really?
我是勇者 真的假的
Yes. You're the chosen hero.
真的 你是被选中的勇者
Hero chosen in a raffle.
抽签抽中的勇者
-A raffle... -Use your hands...
-抽签… -快用你的手…
Huh.
咦
The voice seems to slow down…
声音好像变慢…
Nonsense!
屁啦
Geez. It was your voice.
可恶 原来是你的声音
I anticipated it. What a shame.
我还期待了一下 真丢脸
I'm sorry. Sorry.
对不起 抱歉sorry
I just wanted you to have a dream.
我只是想让你做个美梦
When can I wake up from this nightmare?
我何时才能从恶梦中醒来
Let's pull out the sword first.
就先从拔剑开始吧
That's right.
没错没错
I know I can't, but I'll give it a try.
明知不行 但还是试试看吧
It should be hard to pull this out.
这应该很难拔吧
I can only grab the blade with both hands.
只能用双手夹住刀刃的方法
What's wrong?
怎么了
I feel like I can pull it out.
好像能拔得出来
Is it mistaken belief?
是错觉吧
It should be a mistaken belief.
应该是错觉
Is it your mistaken belief?
是不是你的错觉
You're the ones who have it.
你们才有错觉咧
Geez. I'll pull it out and show you.
可恶 我偏要拔出来给你们看
Is he really the chosen one?
难道他真的是天选之人
When did you sign up?
你什么时候去报名的
I didn't.
我才没去报名啦
He pulled it out!
拔出来了
You're really the chosen one!
你真的是天选之人
No. Look carefully.
不 大家仔细看
MISSED
(没中)
Missed.
没中
What?
什么跟什么啦
Great. You got the sword.
太好了 恭喜得到圣剑
Missed sword.
没中的圣剑
You must think it suits me anyway.
反正你一定觉得很适合我
Just laugh if you want to.
想笑就笑吧
What? Can I? Thank you.
什么 可以吗 谢谢你
Forget it. Don't laugh.
算了 不准笑
Smile is my merit. How mean.
笑容是我的优点耶 过分
Rethink your self introduction.
给我重新思考你的自我介绍
What's left on me after taking off my smile?
拿掉我的笑容后 我还剩什么
The feeling of being beaten.
欠揍的感觉
Honestly. What's wrong with you?
真是的 闹什么别扭啊
Pull yourself together.
打起精神嘛
Mr. Alvin already has a prize named Carla, after all.
毕竟埃尔文先生 已经有个名为卡菈的大奖
How shy.
好害羞
Food poisoning is better than you.
食物中毒都比你好
Now that you have the sword
既然你手上已经有剑了
let's look at the result of your daily training.
让我们看看你平日训练的成果吧
Don't think you can defeat me with the sword.
别以为有剑就能打赢我
Mr. Alvin, you're being looked down on.
埃尔文先生你被瞧不起了
I believe you. The daily training is useless.
我相信你 平日的训练 一点用都没有
Do you know you're making things worse?
你知道你正在火上浇油吗
Don't worry. I'll support you.
不用担心 我会支援你的
Now I'm more worried.
担心的事增加了
Two versus one? That's a good concession.
2比1吗 这个让步条件不错
He's the one to give in.
要让步的对象是他啦
Look at him.
你看他啦
I can't listen to it anymore.
我快听不下去了啦
Although I'm weak, you didn't do your duty as a defender.
我虽然很弱 但你也没做到后卫该尽的责任
You'd only say that.
你就只会这么说
Again.
又来了
Is their relationship good or bad?
他们之间的感情究竟是好是坏
Magic I'm going to use this time.
这次要使用的魔法
Increase defense magic.
提升防御力魔法
Your every move pisses me off.
你的一举一动都很令人不爽
Just use this magic.
只要施展这个魔法
Look. Just like this.
看 就像这样
Like what? You were just clapping your hands.
像哪样 你只是拍拍手而已
Hold on. What are you doing?
等等 你干嘛
What are you...
你要干…
Look. It doesn't hurt, right?
看 不痛吧
But my mind is hurt.
但我的心灵受到打击了
Your body isn't injured at all, right?
肉体没任何损伤吧
It's all thanks to magic.
这都多亏了魔法
It really doesn't hurt.
的确是不痛啦
Companions will not hit hard.
同伴之间 会不自觉地放轻手劲吧
Let me give it a try.
让我试试看吧
Why?
为什么
Take off your armour, anyway. Lie on the ground like a dog.
反正你脱下盔甲 像狗一样趴在地上
Then it's me. My turn.
之后换我 换我哦
I mean why...
我问为什么…
Harry!
哈利
I'm not a chair.
我不是椅子
Let's begin.
开始咯
One more time.
再一下
It's not over yet.
还没结束
Go on.
继续继续
How is it? Say that it feels nice.
怎么样 说你很爽
Miss Dryad. Stop!
德律阿得小姐 停
Is it as painful as you imagined?
有想象中的痛吗
There's something wrong with your imagination.
你的想象才有问题吧
It seems he doesn't feel anything.
好像真的没感觉耶
It's boring.
好无聊
Stop it. It sounds like something else.
别说了 听起来好像有别的意思
Next is my turn.
接下来 换我了
But this magic is awesome. It doesn't hurt at all.
不过这个魔法好厉害 我一点都不痛耶
Right?
对吧
What? So you can cast normal magic.
搞什么 原来你也会正常的魔法
Sexual harassment.
性骚扰
It'd be nice if you had a better personality.
性格再好点就好了
It's my turn. My turn.
换我 换我了
I'm not a sandbag.
我不是沙包
Forget it. Thanks to Carla's magic, I can finally fight you this time.
算了 多亏卡菈的魔法 这次终于能跟你一决胜负了
And I have a sword in my hand.
而且我手中也有剑
You have to hurry up.
动作要快哦
When the magic loses its effect, it'll backfire twice the harm.
魔法失效后 会反噬两倍的伤害
Or ten times?
还是十倍啊
It's my turn!
换我了啦
It tastes good.
好好吃
It's delicious.
真美味
Great. It suits your taste.
太好了 合你们的口味
I made the cake using the fruits from this forest.
我用这座森林的果实做成的蛋糕
You have a terrible fetish, but you're feminine.
你的性癖虽然很糟 但却很有女人味
What a noisy reptile.
好吵的爬虫类
It's like the smell of a flower blooming next to a wind god surrounded by a group
简直就像为了吹拂诅咒之地 阻挡瘴气暴风而建造的神殿中
of vegetable insects in a temple built to blow the cursed land and stop the miasma storm.
在某位风神旁绽放的一朵花 被一群菜虫围绕的味道
Is that a compliment?
这不是夸奖吧
Oh, right. Is Mr. Alvin okay?
对了 埃尔文先生还好吗
He'll wake up soon.
等等就会醒了
Because I drew the holy recovery magic array for him.
因为我帮他画了神圣的恢复魔法阵
Thank you for lending me your room, Miss Dryad.
谢谢你借我房间 德律阿得小姐
You're welcome. It's also a kind of fate.
不客气 这也是一种缘分嘛
This girl party is really a strange fate.
这个女生聚会的确是奇怪的缘分
Speaking of fate, why did Carla team up with Alvin?
说到缘分 卡菈为何跟埃尔文组队
How should I put it?
怎么说呢
The vanguard is such a weak warrior. What's the advantage of forming a party with him?
前卫是这么弱的战士 跟他组队有何好处
I know he's nice.
我知道他人不错
But it's a little troublesome with him as a teammate.
但当队友的话 就有点碍事了
I didn't expect you two to live to this day.
没想到你们能活到现在
Sorry, I'm not talking ill of your partner.
抱歉 我并不是在说你同伴的坏话
Can I have another piece of cake?
能再给我一份蛋糕吗
Okay.
好
I know what you're trying to say.
我懂两位想说什么
But Mr. Alvin has many good points, such as
但埃尔文先生并不会对 "最弱鲁蛇之王"的称号
he won't be ashamed of the title "The Weakest King of Loser".
感到丢脸等许多优点哦
He should feel ashamed of it.
应该要感到丢脸吧
For instance...
比方说
Can't you think of the first one?
才第一个就想不到了吗
-Pathetic. -You're speaking ill of him.
-可悲 -你是在说他的坏话
-Miserable. -This too.
-悲惨 -这也是
-Poor. -This as well.
-可怜
That's not it.
不是这样的
You'd better say nothing.
你还是什么都别说吧
I feel happy when I'm with him.
跟他在一起觉得很开心
What are you talking about?
你们在说什么
You... didn't scare me. Not at all.
你…才没吓到我 完全没有
You look very shocked.
你看起来受到极大的惊吓
Did you hear what we said?
你听到我们说的话了吗
No, I only heard your voices.
没 只听到说话声
We were talking about you.
我们在说你的事
About me?
我的事
Speaking ill of me, anyway.
反正是在说坏话吧
Something like pathetic, miserable and poor.
可悲 悲惨 可怜之类的
All correct.
全对
But Carla also said...
不过 卡菈还说…
You scared me. What's wrong?
吓死我了 干嘛啦
There was a shooting star just now.
刚才 有流星
It's indoor.
这里是室内
Sorry. Please say it again.
抱歉 请再说一次
You're so noisy.
你很吵耶
Wow. Shooting star.
Wow Shooting Star
Even if you speak English, it's still indoor.
就算说英文 这里还是室内
What's wrong? Is there something I can't hear?
干什么啦 是什么不能让我听的内容吗
Nothing.
没什么
Then keep quiet.
那你就给我安静点
So what exactly have you said?
所以 你们到底说了什么
Well...
这个嘛…
Sorry. I suddenly forgot it.
抱歉 我突然忘记了
You forgot it as soon as it was said?
才刚说完就忘了吗
I remember it clearly.
我记得一清二楚哦
-Stop it. -Alvin, listen.
-别说了 -埃尔文 听着
Carla thinks when she's with you...
卡菈觉得跟你在一起…
A... Choo!
哈 啾
Oh, no. I just sneezed.
糟糕 不小心打了个喷嚏
Who'd sneeze and use Tetsuzanko at the same time?
哪有人边打喷嚏边使出铁山靠啦
STILL TEN YEARS EARLY
(还早十年呢)
"NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW" Title of the next episode...
(下集预告) 下集的标题…
"THE SECOND HALF OF THIS EPISODE FINALLY GETS TO THE CONTENT OF "WHAT'S THIS STORY"." Dryad!
(这集后半段终于进入"这是什么故事"的内容了) 德律阿得
"(STILL, BUT ONLY THIS TIME AND NEXT TIME.) I'LL EXPLAIN IT AGAIN IN CASE SOMEONE DOESN'T KNOW." Me too.
((话虽如此但也只有这次和下次两次而已) 怕有人不知道所以再说明一次) 我也要我也要
""WHAT'S THIS STORY" IS THE STORY BEFORE THIS STORY BECAME "DON'T HURT ME, MY HEALER"." I want to report the title too.
("这是什么故事"是本故事变成"这个僧侣有点烦"之前) 我也要一起报标题
"THAT'S THE STORY POSTED ON THE ONLINE SUBMISSION WEBSITE BEFORE SERIALIZATION. ALTHOUGH IT HASN'T BEEN" Medusa.
(也就是在连载之前放在网络投稿网站的故事 所以虽然还没收录在漫画中) 梅杜莎
"INCLUDED IN THE COMIC, YOU MAY READ IT ON THE INTERNET. PLEASE READ IT ONLINE IF YOU WANT." Don't bother me.
(但应该还能在网络上看得到 想看的话请上网看) 别来碍事
"BUT THERE'S A WICKED CHARACTER IN THE FIRST HALF THAT YOU CAN'T MISS. THE REASON WHY YOU SHOULD" Go away.
(不过前半段有位绝不能错过的可恨角色登场 之所以请大家务必注意的原因是) 你去旁边
"PAY ATTENTION IS... YOU'LL KNOW IF YOU CONTINUE TO WATCH IT. IN SHORT," Play "hah" by yourself.
(今后继续看下去就懂了 总之有许多内容的第十话) 自己玩"喝"
"THERE ARE MANY CONTENTS IN EPISODE TEN. STAY TUNED." I don't want to.
(要继续观看哦) 不要不要
-Let me do it too. -You're annoying.
-我也要啦 -你很吵耶
-Let's report the title together. -I myself...
-一起报标题啦 -我自己…